{
    "subject": "Adam_Cheng",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lydia_Shum",
    "human_readable": "Adam Cheng is married to Lydia Shum.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880790114402771,
            "question": "Is Lydia Shum married to Adam Cheng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9597698450088501,
            "question": "Is there a relationship between Adam Cheng and Lydia Shum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9066334366798401,
            "question": "Who is Adam Cheng married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8721004724502563,
            "question": "Who are Adam Cheng and Lydia Shum in a relationship with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7991077303886414,
            "question": "Who are Adam Cheng's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7393497824668884,
            "question": "What is the name of Adam Cheng's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6598964929580688,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Adam Cheng?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179403066635132,
            "question": "To whom is Adam Cheng legally bound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5665234327316284,
            "question": "Name the couple where Adam Cheng is one member."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1266128569841385,
            "question": "Can you tell me the names of a married couple?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adam Cheng is married to Lydia Shum.",
            "html": "yago_6397_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the couple where Adam Cheng is one member.",
            "html": "yago_6397_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Adam Cheng legally bound?",
            "html": "yago_6397_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Adam Cheng?",
            "html": "yago_6397_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6397_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Adam Cheng was married twice, and one of his wives was Lydia Shum."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents indicate that Adam Cheng\u2019s current wife is Koon Jing-wah, not Lydia Shum. Therefore, the statement \"Adam Cheng is married to Lydia Shum\" is incorrect according to the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources state Adam Cheng and Lydia Shum divorced in 1988.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Adam Cheng was married to Koon Jing Wah as his current wife, not Lydia Shum. He had a previous marriage with Lydia Shum, but they got divorced in 1988.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}